<Mod
	name="Noitavania"
	description="Noitavania is a vanilla-friendly (kinda) map expansion project that fills once empty space with new and expanded biomes, aiming to provide a metroidvania-like world experience, as well as providing a new and interesting map challenge for Nightmare/NG+.\n\n[h1]What does this mod do?[/h1]\n[list][*] Opens up the map with more inter-biome connectivity.\n[*] Greatly expands previously empty areas with new and returning biomes, created by myself and other members of the modding community.\n[*] Reworks the cavernous and empty areas of the vanilla map to have stuff to actually do besides fall asleep as you dig through miles of Extremely Dense Rock.\n[*] Adds additional secrets and rewards across the map.\n[*]Adds a sprawling Nightmare/NG+ map alternative, with an almost entirely different approach to the map design. (*Really* departed from vanilla)\n[*]Adds mini-temples to the expanded side areas to encourage and reward the brave explorer.\n[*]Adds new mini-bosses with custom sprites, found in the furtherst parts of the map. (Currently only includes a half-finished boss in the Dark Castle. Updates coming soon!)\n[*]Works with Horscht's [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2227903743]Location Tracker[/url]! (Minimap Mod)[/list]\n[h2]New biomes added[/h2]\nSewers, Storage Depot, Cryo-Storage,\nVolcano, Space, Toxic Dump,\nCursed Tunnel, Dark Castle, Hive,\nForgotten Tunnels, Ruined Bunker *and maybe more to come...*\n\n[url=https://easyzoom.com/image/243831]1.21 Map Capture[/url] ((Big thanks to mzx987 for the 1.21 Map Capture!))\n[url=https://easyzoom.com/image/243834]1.19 NG+/Nightmare Map Capture[/url] (OLD and missing some spots, but mostly accurate.)\n[h2]Credits & Thanks[/h2]\nThanks for Everfades and Horscht for the amazing pictures! I am truly blessed.\nThanks to Horscht (Author of the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2028431626]Volcano[/url] biome), Perh (Author of [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1976633201]Sewer+[/url]), Archaeopteryx/HornedKey (Author of [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1985575640]New Biomes + Secrets[/url]), and Congress (Author of [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2334635191]Chasm Biomes[/url]) for the permission to adapt and modify their biomes!\n\nFind the latest development version of the mod [url=https://github.com/Tanksy/Noitavania]Here![/url]\nWant to support my mods? [url=https://ko-fi.com/tanksy]Buy me a Coffee![/url]"
	tags="gameplay,biomes"
	dont_upload_folders=""
	dont_upload_files=""
	> 
</Mod>